Guide to the TV Tie-in Book Collection, 1945-1999
TV Tie-in Book Collection, 1945-1999
- The Shari Lewis Show: Fun With the Kids by Shari Lewis Macfaddens 75-140 ca. 1960 (1st: 1964) (Box 34)
- The Silent Force by Harry Goddard Popular Library 01418 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 34)
- The Silent Service by William C. Chambliss Signet S1658 ca. 1959 (1st) (Box 34)
- Cyborg by Martin Caidin Warner 76-643 ca. 1972 (2nd: 1974) (Box 34)
- Cyborg by Martin Caidin Warner 88-371 ca. 1972 (3rd: 1976) (Variant Cover) (Box 34)
- Cyborg #2: Operation Nuke by Martin Caidin Warner 76-061 ca. 1973 (1st: 1974) (Box 34)
- The Six Million Dollar Man #1: Wine, Women and War by Michael Jahn Warner 76-833 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 34)
- The Six Million Dollar Man #2: Solid Gold Kidnapping by Evan Richards [Michael Jahn] Warner 76-834 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 34)
- The Six Million Dollar Man #3: High Crystal by Martin Caidin Warner 76-408 ca. 1974 (1st: 1975) (Box 34)
- The Six Million Dollar Man #4: Pilot Error by Martin Caidin Warner 76-835 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 34)
- The Six Million Dollar Man #5: The Rescue of Athena One by Michael Jahn Warner 76-836 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 34)
- The Six Million Dollar Man #6: CYBORG IV by Martin Caidin Warner 76-655 ca. 1975 (1st: 1976) (Box 34)
- The Six Million Dollar Man: The Secret of Bigfoot Pass by Michael Jahn Berkley Z3307 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 34)
- The Six Million Dollar Man: International incidents by Michael Jahn Berkley 03331 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 34)
- The Six Million Dollar Man's Bionic Brain Benders by Rose Paul Tempo 12523 ca. 1975,76 (1st: 1976) (Box 34)
- The Sixth Sense #1: Witch, Witch, Burning Bright by Jon W. Bloch Tempo 05570 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 34)
- The $64,000 Question Official Quiz Book by Louis G. Cowan, ed. Dell First Edition 79 ca. 1955 (1st) (Box 34)
- The Smith Family #1: Meet the Smiths by Norman Daniels Berkley X2127 ca. 1971 (1st: 1972) (Box 34)
- Sons and Daughters by William Johnston Ballantine 24235 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 34)
- Space: 1999 #1: Breakaway by E.C. Tubb Pocket 80184 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 34)
- Space: 1999 #2: Moon Odyssey by John Rankine Pocket 80185 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 34)
- Space: 1999 #3: Space guardians by Brian Ball Pocket 80198 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 34)
- Space: 1999 #4: Collision Course by E.C. Tubb Pocket 80274 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 34)
- Space: 1999 #5: Lunar Attack by John Rankine Pocket 80305 ca. 1975 (1st: 1976) (Box 34)
- Space: 1999 #6: Astral Quest by John Rankine Pocket 80392 ca. 1975 (1st: 1976) (Box 34)
- Space: 1999 #7: Alien Seed by E.C. Tubb Pocket 80520 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 34)
- Space: 1999 #8: Android Planet by John Rankine Pocket 80706 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 34)
- Space: 1999 #9: Rogue Planet by E.C. Tubb Pocket 80710 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 34)
- Space: 1999 #10: Phoenix of Megaron by John Rankine Pocket 80764 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 34)
- Space: 1999 (Year 2) #1: Planet of Peril by Michael Butterworth Warner 88-341 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 35)
- Space: 1999 #1: Planet of Peril by Michael Butterworth Warner Star ca. 1977 (Box 35)
- Space: 1999 (Year 2) #2: Mind-Breaks of Space by Michael Butterworth Warner 88-342 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 35)
- Space: 1999 #2: Mind-Breaks of Space by Michael Butterworth Star ca. 1977 (Box 35)
- Space: 1999 (Year 2) #3: The Space-Jackers by Michael Butterworth Warner 88-343 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 35)
- Space: 1999 (Year 2) #4: The Psychomorph by Michael Butterworth Warner 88-344 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 35)
- Space: 1999 (Year 2) #5: The Time Fighters by Michael Butterworth Warner 88-345 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 35)
- Space: 1999 (Year 2) #6: The Edge of Infinite by Michael Butterworth Warner 88-346 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 35)
- The Making of Space: 1999 by Tim Heald Ballantine 25265 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 35)
- Spenser: For Hire: Valediction by Robert B. Parker Dell 19246 ca. 1984 (4th: 1986) (Box 35)
- Spencer: For Hire: God Save the Child by Robert B. Parker Dell 12899 ca. 1974 (Box 35)
- Star Trek by James Blish Bantam F3459 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 35)
- Star Trek 1 by James Blish Bantam 02114 ca. 1967 (Box 35)
- Star Trek 2 by James Blish Bantam F3439 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 35)
- Star Trek 2 by James Blish Bantam F3439 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 35)
- Star Trek 3 by James Blish Bantam F4371 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 35)
- Star Trek 4 by James Blish Bantam S7009 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 35)
- Star Trek 5 by James Blish Bantam S7300 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 35)
- Star Trek 6 by James Blish Bantam S7364 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 35)
- Star Trek 7 by James Blish Bantam S7480 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 35)
- Star Trek 8 by James Blish Bantam SP7550 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 35)
- Star Trek 9 by James Blish Bantam SP7808 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 35)
- Star Trek 10 by James Blish Bantam SP8401 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 35)
- Star Trek 11 by James Blish Bantam Q8717 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 35)
- Star Trek 12 by James Blish and J.A. Lawrence Bantam 11382 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 35)
- Spock Must Die! by James Blish Bantam H5515 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 35)
- Mudd's Angels by J.A. Lawrence Bantam 11802 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 35)
- Star Trek Fotonovel #1: City on the Edge of Forever Bantam 11345 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 35)
- Star Trek Fotonovel #2: Where No Man Has Gone Before Bantam 11346 ca. 1965,77 (1st: 1977) (Box 35)
- Star Trek Fotonovel #3: The rouble With Tribbles Bantam 11347 ca. 1967,77 (1st: 1977) (Box 35)
- Star Trek Fotonovel #4: A Taste of Armageddon Bantam 11348 ca. 1967,77 (1st: 1978) (Box 35)
- Star Trek Fotonovel #5: Metamorphosis Bantam 11349 ca. 1967,78 (1st: 1978) (Box 36)
- Star Trek Fotonovel #6: All Our Yesterdays Bantam 11350 ca. 1969,78 (1st: 1978) (Box 36)
- Star Trek Fotonovel #7: The Galileo Seven Bantam 12041 ca. 1967,78 (1st: 1978) (Box 36)
- Star Trek Fotonovel #8: A Piece of the Action Bantam 12022 ca. 1968,78 (1st: 1978) (Box 36)
- Star Trek Fotonovel #9: The Devil in the Dark Bantam 12021 ca. 1967,78 (1st: 1978) (Box 36)
- Star Trek Fotonovel #10: Day of the Dove Bantam 12017 ca. 1968,78 (1st: 1978) (Box 36)
- Star Trek Fotonovel #11: The Deadly Years Bantam 12028 ca. 1967,78 (1st: 1978) (Box 36)
- Star Trek Fotonovel #12: Amok Time Bantam 12012 ca. 1967,78 (1st: 1978) (Box 36)
- The Making of Stat Trek by Stephen E. Whitfield and Gene Roddenberry Ballantine 73004 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 36)
- The World of Star Trek by David Gerrold Ballantine 23403 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 36)
- Star Trek Log One by Alan Dean Foster Ballantine 24014 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 36)
- Star Trek Log Two by Alan Dean Foster Ballantine 24184 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 36)
- Star Trek Log Three by Alan Dean Foster Ballantine 24260 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 36)
- Star Trek Log Four by Alan Dean Foster Ballantine 24435 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 36)
- Star Trek Log Five by Alan Dean Foster Ballantine 24532 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 36)
- Star Trek Log Six by Alan Dean Foster Ballantine 24655 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 36)
- Star Trek Log Seven by Alan Dean Foster Ballantine 24965 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 36)
- Star Trek Log Eight by Alan Dean Foster Ballantine 25141 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 36)
- Star Trek Log Nine by Alan Dean Foster Ballantine 25557 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 36)
- Star Trek Log Ten by Alan Dean Foster Ballantine 27212 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 36)
- Star Trek: The Next Generation: Encounter at Farpoint by David Gerrold Pocket 65241 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 36)
- Star Trek: The Next Generation #1: Ghost Ship by Diane Carey Pocket 66579 ca. 1988 (1st) (Box 36)
- Star Trek: The Next Generation #2: The Peacekeepers by Gene DeWeese Pocket 66929 ca. 1988 (1st) (Box 36)
- Star Trek: The Next Generation #3: The Children of Hamlin by Carmen Carter Pocket 67319 ca. 1988 (1st) (Box 36)
- Star Trek: The Next Generation #4: Survivors by Jean Lorrah Pocket 67438 ca. 1989 (1st) (Box 36)
- Star Trek: The Next Generation #5: Strike Zone by peter David Pocket 67940 ca. 1989 (1st) (Box 36)
- Star Trek: The Next Generation #6: Power hungry by Howard Weinstein Pocket 67714 ca. 1989 (1st) (Box 37)
- Star Trek: The Next Generation #7: Masks by John Vornholt Pocket 67980 ca. 1989 (1st) (Box 37)
- Star Trek: The Next Generation #8: The Captain's Honor by David and Daniel Dvorkin Pocket 68487 ca. 1989 (1st) (Box 37)
- Star Trek: The Next Generation #9: Call to Darkness by Michael Jan Friedman Pocket 68708 ca. 1989 (1st) (Box 37)
- Star Trek: The Next Generation #10: A Rock and a Hard Place by Peter David Pocket 69364 ca. 1990 (1st) (Box 37)
- Starlost: Phoenix Without Ashes by Edward Bryant & Harlan Ellison Fawcett Gold Medal M3188 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 37)
- Starsky and Hutch by Max Franklin [Richard Deming] Ballantine 24996 ca. 1975 (1st: 1976) (Box 37)
- Starsky and Hutch #2: Kill Huggy Bear by Max Franklin [Richard Deming] Ballantine 25124 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 37)
- Starsky and Hutch #3: Death Ride by Max Franklin [Richard Deming] Ballantine 23921 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 37)
- Starsky and Hutch #4: Bounty Hunter by Max Franklin [Richard Deming] Ballantine 25669 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 37)
- Starsky and Hutch #5: Terror on the Docks by Max Franklin [Richard Deming] Ballantine 25709 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 37)
- Starsky and Hutch #6: The Psychic by Max Franklin [Richard Deming] Ballantine 25701 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 37)
- Starsky and Hutch #7: The Set-Up by Max Franklin [Richard Deming] Ballantine 27340 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 37)
- Starsky and Hutch #8 by Max Franklin [Richard Deming] Ballantine 27341 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 37)
- Storefront Lawyers by A.L. Conroy Bantam S5883 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 37)
- Strange Paradise #1 by Dorothy Daniels Paperback Library 63-259 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 37)
- Strange Paradise #2: Island of Evil by Dorothy Daniels Paperback Library 63-321 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 37)
- Strange Paradise #3: Raxl, Voodoo Priestess by Dorothy Daniels Paperback Library 63-365 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 37)
- Strange Report by John Burke Lancer 73219 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 37)
- SurfSide 6 by J.M. Flynn Dell First Edition 8388 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 37)
- Switch by Mike Jahn Berkley Z3082 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 37)
- Switch #2: Round Up the Usual Suspects by Mike Jahn Berkley Z3252 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 37)
- Tales From the Darkside, Vol. 1 by Mitchell Galin and Tom Allen, eds. Berkley 11095 ca. 1988 (1st) (Box 37)
- Tales of Wells Fargo by Frank Gruber Bantam 1726 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 37)
- Tammy Tell Me the Truth by Cid Ricketts Sumner Popular Library 50-439 ca. 1959 (unsp: 1965) (Box 37)
- Tammy in Rome by Cid Ricketts Sumner Popular Library SP423 ca. 1965 (1st) (Box 37)
- Tarzan of the Apes by Edgar Rice Burroughs Ballantine U2001 ca. 1912 (3rd: 1966) (Box 37)
- The Return of Tarzan by Edgar Rice Burroughs Ballantine U2002 ca. 1913 (3rd: 1967) (Box 37)
- That Girl by Paul W. Fairman Popular Library 02588 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 38)
- That's Incredible! Vol. 1 by Wendy Jeffries, ed. Jove B5807 ca. 1980 (1st) (Box 38)
- That's Incredible! Vol. 2 by Wendy Jeffries, ed. Jove B5870 ca. 1981 (1st) (Box 38)
- That's Incredible! Vol. 3 by Wendy Jeffries, ed. Jove B5986 ca. 1981 (1st) (Box 38)
- That's Incredible! Vol. 4 by Wendy Jeffries, ed. Jove 06171 ca. 1981 (1st) (Box 38)
- That's Incredible! Vol. 5 by Wendy Jeffries, ed. Jove 06172 ca. 1981 (1st) (Box 38)
- That's Incredible! Vol. 6 by Wendy Jeffries, ed. Jove 06173 ca. 1981 (1st) (Box 38)
- Then Came Bronson by William Johnston Pyramid T02106 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 38)
- The Came Bronson #2: The Ticket by Chris Stratton [Richard Hubbard] Pyramid T-2213 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 38)
- The Came Bronson #3: Rock! by Chris Stratton [Richard Hubbard] Pyramid T2259 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 38)
- The Third Man by Graham Greene Bantam J2427 ca. 1949,50 (1st new Bantam: 1962) (Box 38)
- This Man Dawson by Henry E. Helseth Signet S2109 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 38)
- Thunder: The Mighty Stallion of the Hills by Mike Jahn Tempo 14893 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 38)
- Thunder: The Mighty Stallion to the Rescue by Mike Jahn Tempo 14894 ca. 1979 (1st) (Box 38)
- The Time Tunnel [illustrated cover] by Murray Leinster [Will F. Jenkins] Pyramid R-1522 ca. 1966 (1st: 1967) (Box 38)
- The Time Tunnel [illustrated cover] by Murray Leinster [Will F. Jenkins] Pyramid R-1522 ca. 1966 (1st: 1967) (Second Copy) (Box 38)
- The Time Tunnel [photo cover] by Murray Leinster [Will F. Jenkins] Pyramid R-1522 ca. 1966 (1st: 1967) (Box 38)
- The Time Tunnel #2: Timeslip! by Murray Leinster [Will F. Jenkins] Pyramid R-1680 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 38)
- Toma by David Toma with Michael Brett Dell 08520 ca. 1973 (1st: 1974) (Box 38)
- Toma #2: The Airport Affair by David Toma with Jack Pearl Dell 04604 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 38)
- Toma #3: The Affair of the Unhappy Hooker by David Toma with Jack Pearl Dell 05284 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 38)
- Happiness is a Dry Martini by Johnny Carson Crest T1217 ca. 1965 (1st: 1968) (Box 38)
- and now Here's Johnny! by Nora Ephron Avon V2251 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 38)
- Tonight! by Terry Galanoy Warner 76-367 ca. 1972 (1st (Box 38)
- 1974) (Box 38)
- He-e-e-ere's Johnny by Robert Lardine Award AD1425 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 38)
- Johnny Tonight! by Craig Tennis Pocket 41451 ca. 1980 (1st) (Box 38)
- King of the Night: The Life of Johnny Carson by Laurence Leamer St. Martin's Press 92256 ca. 1989 (1st: 1990) (Box 38)
- Ed McMahon's Barside Companion by J.P. Tarcher, ed Pocket 77215 ca. 1969 (1st: 1970) (Box 38)
- Grin and Beer It by Ed McMahon Pyramid N4101 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 39)
- Here's Ed by Ed McMahon Berkley 03592 ca. 1976 (1st: 1977) (Box 39)
- Trials of O'Brien by Robert L. Fish Signet D2821 ca. 1965 (1st) (Box 39)
- Twelve O'Clock High! by Beirne Lay, Jr. and Sy Bartlett Ballantine U5041 ca. 1948 (1st: 1965) (Box 39)
- Twenty-One Pyramid G322 ca. 1957 (1st: 1958) (Box 39)
- Stories From the Twilight Zone by Rod Serling Bantam A2046 ca. 1960 (1st) (Box 39)
- More Stories From the Twilight Zone by Rod Serling Bantam A2227 ca. 1961 (1st) (Box 39)
- New Stories From the Twilight Zone by Rod Serling Bantam A2412 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 39)
- Chilling Stories From Rod Serling's The Twilight Zone by Walter B. Gibson Tempo T89 ca. 1963 (1st: 1965) (Box 39)
- Rod Serling's Twilight Zone Revisited by Walter B. Gibson Tempo T-171 ca. 1964 (1st: 1967) (Box 39)
- UFO-1: Flesh Hunters by Robert Miall [John Burke] Warner 75-273 ca. 1970 (1st: 1973) (Box 39)
- UFO-2: Sporting Blood by Robert Miall [John Burke] Warner 75-274 ca. 1971 (1st: 1973) (Box 39)
- The Ugliest Girl in Town by Burt Hirschfeld Popular Library 60-2340 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 39)
- The Untouchables by Eliot Ness and Oscar Fraley Popular Library G403 ca. 1957 (1st: 1960) (Box 39)
- The Untouchables [cover-variation] by Eliot Ness and Oscar Fraley Popular Library SP258 ca. 1957 (unsp: 1964) (Box 39)
- The Untouchables: 4 Against the Mob by Oscar Fraley Popular Library G512 ca. 1961 (1st) (Box 39)
- The Last of the Untouchables by Oscar Fraley and Paul Robsky Popular Library G569 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 39)
- V by A.C. Crispin Pinnacle 42237 ca. 1984 (1st) (Box 39)
- V: East Coast Crisis by Howard Weinstein and A.C. Crispin Pinnacle 42259 ca. 1984 (1st) (Box 39)
- V: The Pursuit of Diana by Allen Wold Pinnacle 42401 ca. 1984 (1st) (Box 39)
- V: The Chicago Conversion by Geo. W. Proctor Pinnacle 42429 ca. 1985 (1st) (Box 39)
- V: The Florida Project by Tim Sullivan Pinnacle 42430 ca. 1985 (1st) (Box 39)
- V: Prisoners and Pawns by Howard Weinstein Pinnacle 42439 ca. 1985 (1st) (Box 39)
- V: The Alien Swordmaster by Somtow Sucharitkul Pinnacle 42441 ca. 1985 (1st) (Box 39)
- V: The Crivit Experiment by Allen Wold Pinnacle 42466 ca. 1985 (1st) (Box 39)
- V: The New England Resistance by Tim Sullivan Pinnacle 42467 ca. 1985 (1st) (Box 39)
- V: Death Tide by A.C. Crispin and Deborah A. Marshall Pinnacle 42469 ca. 1985 (1st) (Box 39)
- V: The Texas Run by Geo. W. Proctor Pinnacle 42470 ca. 1985 (1st) (Box 40)
- V: Symphony of Terror by Somtow Sucharitkul Tor 55482 ca. 1988 (1st) (Box 40)
- V: Path to Conquest by Howard Weinstein Tor 55725 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 40)
- V: To Conquer the Throne by Tim Sullivan Tor 55727 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 40)
- V: The Oregon Invasion by Jane Tannehill Tor 55729 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 40)
- V: Below the Threshold by Allen Wold Tor 55732 ca. 1988 (1st) (Box 40)
- Vegas$ by Max Franklin [Richard Deming] Ballantine 28051 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 40)
- The Virginian by Owen Wister Paperback Library 53-190 ca. 1902 (1st: 1963) (Box 40)
- The Virginian by Owen Wister Paperback Library 53-908 ca. 1902 (2nd: 1965) (Box 40)
- The Virginian by Owen Wister Paperback Library 64-405 ca. 1902 (3rd: 1970) (Box 40)
- The Virginian by Owen Wister Magnum 14642 ca. 1902 (1st: 1970) (Box 40)
- Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea by Theodore Sturgeon Pyramid R-1068 ca. 1961 (2nd: 1964) (Box 40)
- Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea: City Under the Sea by Paul W. Fairman Pyramid R-1162 ca. 1965 (1st) (Box 40)
- Voyager! by Joe Claro Scholastic Book Services 32740 ca. 1982 (1st) (Box 40)
- The Wackiest Ship in the Army by Lee Bergman Popular Library PC1056 ca. 1965 (1st) (Box 40)
- Wagon Train: Wagonmaster by Robert Turner Pocket 1196 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 40)
- Wagon Train: The Scout by Robert Turner Pocket 1216 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 40)
- Wagons West! by Robert Turner Pocket 1226 ca. 1959 (1st) (Box 40)
- The Walt Disney Story of Our Friend the Atom by Heinz Haber, Ph.D. Dell First Edition B104 ca. 1956 (1st) (Box 40)
- The Story of Walt Disney by Diane Disney Miller as told to Pete Martin Dell D266 ca. 1956,57 (1st: 1959) (Box 40)
- The Life of Davy Crockett by Davy Crockett Signet S1214 ca. 1955 (1st) (Box 40)
- Spencer's Mountain by Earl Hamner, Jr. Dell 08180 ca. 1961 (1st new Dell: 1973) (Box 40)
- Spencer's Mountain by Earl Hamner, Jr. Dell 08180 ca. 1961 (Variant Cover) (Box 40)
- The Homecoming by Earl Hamner, Jr. Avon 15149 ca. 1970 (1st: 1973) (Box 40)
- The Homecoming by Earl Hamner, Jr. Avon 15149 ca. 1970 (1st: 1973) (Variant Cover) (Box 40)
- The Waltons by Robert Weverka Bantam NP6302 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 40)
- The Waltons: Trouble on the Mountain by Robert Weverka Bantam N2280 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 41)
- The Walton: Easter Story by Robert Weverka Bantam Q2411 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 41)
- The Walton: Easter Story by Robert Weverka Bantam 9438 ca. 1976 (1st) (Variant Cover) (Box 41)
- The Walton Family Cookbook Sylvia Resnick Bantam TE2123 ca. 1975 (1st: 1976) (Box 41)
- Wanted: Dead or Alive by Frank Robertson Signet S1982 ca. 1961 (1st) (Box 41)
- Welcome Back, Kotter #1: The Sweathog Trail by William Johnston Tempo 12406 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 41)
- Welcome Back, Kotter #1: The Sweathog Trail by William Johnston Ace Tempo Star 79114 ca. 1976 (1st Tempo Star: 1977) (Box 41)
- Welcome Back, Kotter #2: The Sweathog Newshawks by William Johnston Tempo 12407 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 41)
- Welcome Back, Kotter #3: The Super Sweathogs by William Johnston Tempo 12608 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 41)
- Welcome Back, Kotter #4: 10-4 Sweathogs! by William Johnston Tempo 12706 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 41)
- Welcome Back, Kotter #5: The Sweathog Sit-In by William Johnston Tempo 12944 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 41)
- Welcome Back, Kotter #6: Barbarino Drops Out by William Johnston Tempo 12945 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 41)
- Meet John Travolta by Suzanne Munshower Tempo 12936 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 41)
- John Travolta by Suzanne Munshower Ace Tempo Star 40630 ca. 1976,78 (1st: 1978) (Box 41)
- What are the Odds? by Leo Guild Crest 369 ca. 1960 (1st) (Box 41)
- Wheel of Fortune by David R. Sams and Robert L. Shook St. Martin's Press 90833 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 41)
- Vanna White by Marianne Robin-Tani St. Martin's Press 90829 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 41)
- Vanna Speaks by Vanna White with Patricia Romanowski Warner 34668 ca. 1987 (1st: 1988) (Box 41)
- The Official Wheel of Fortune Puzzle Book by Nancy Jones Bantam 27204 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 41)
- The Wild Wild West by Richard Wormser Signet D2836 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 41)
- The Young and the Restless: The Story of Chris and Snapper by Deborah Sherwood Bantam Q2556 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 41)
- The Young and the Restless: The Story of Brad and Leslie by Deborah Sherwood Bantam 10115 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 41)
- The Young and the Restless #2: Bold Passions by Angelica Aimes [Lita Scott] Pioneer 72 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 41)
- The Young and the Restless #3: Echoes of Love by Angelica Aimes [Lita Scott] Pioneer 73 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 41)
- The Young and the Restless #4: A Touch of Paradise by Angelica Aimes [Lita Scott] Pioneer 74 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 41)
- The Young and the Restless #6: Bittersweet Harvest by Catherine Wheelright Pioneer 30 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 41)
- The Young and the Restless #7: One Shining Moment by Catherine Wheelright Pioneer 77 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 41)
- The Young and the Restless #8: Far Side of Love by Elizabeth Summers Pioneer 78 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 41)
- The Young and the Restless #9: The Highest Price by Angelica Aimes [Lita Scott] Pioneer 79 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 41)
- The Young and the Restless #11: Whirlwind by Erika Bryant Pioneer 250 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 42)
- The Young and the Restless #12: Paradise Found by Erika Bryant Pioneer 251 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 42)
- The Young and the Restless #13: Passion's Pride by Charlotte Granville Pioneer 252 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 42)
- The Young and the Restless #14: Free Spirit by Erika Bryant Pioneer 253 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 42)
- Young Dr. Kildare by Max Brand Beagle 95254 ca. 1938,41 (1st: 1972) (Box 42)
- Dr. Kildare's Trial by Max Brand Beagle 95255 ca. 1941,42 (1st: 1972) (Box 42)
- Dr. Kildare Takes Charge by Max Brand Beagle 95256 ca. 1940,41 (1st: 1972) (Box 42)
- Calling Dr. Kildare by Max Brand Beagle 95274 ca. 1939,40 (1st: 1972) (Box 42)
- The Secret of Dr. Kildare by Max Brand Beagle 95275 ca. 1939,40 (1st: 1972) (Box 42)
- Dr. Kildare's Crisis by Max Brand Beagle 95276 ca. 1940,41 (1st: 1972) (Box 42)
- Dr. Kildare's Search by Max Brand Beagle 95277 ca. 1940+ (1st: 1972) (Box 42)
- The Young Lawyers: Test Case by B.D. Ashe Dell 08629 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 42)
- The Young Rebels #1: The Hedgerow Incident by William Johnston Ace 32335 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 42)
- The Young Rebels #2: The Sea Gold Incident by William Johnston Ace 95051 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 42)
- Zcars: Barlow on Trial by Ian Kennedy Martin World Distributors 801 ca. 1965 (Box 42)
- The Mark of Zorro by Johnston McCulley Dell D204 ca. 1924,52 (1st new Dell: 1958) (Box 42)
- The Mark of Zorro by Johnston McCulley Dell 553 ca. 1924 (Box 42)
- Batman and Robin in the Cheetah Caper by George S. Elrick Whitman Big Little Book 2031 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 42)
- Bonanza: The Bubble Gum Kid by George S. Elrick Whitman Big Little Book 2002 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 42)
- The Buccaneers by Alice Sankey Whitman Big Little Book 1646 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 42)
- Daktari: Night of Terror by George S. Elrick Whitman Big Little Book 2018 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 42)
- The Flinstones: The Case of the Many Missing Things by Paul S. Newman Whitman Big Little Book 2014 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 42)
- "flipper": Killer Whale Trouble by George S. Elrick Whitman Big Little Book 2003 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 42)
- "flipper": Deep-Sea Photographer by George S. Elrick Whitman Big Little Book 2032 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 42)
- Gentle Ben: Mystery in the Everglades by Paul S. Newman Whitman Big Little Book 2035 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 42)
- Gunsmoke by Doris Schroeder Whitman Big Little Book 1647 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 43)
- The Invaders: Alien Missile Threat by Paul S. Newman Whitman Big Little Book 2012 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 43)
- The Adventures of Jim Bowie by Lewis B. Patten Whitman Big Little Book 1648 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 43)
- Lassie: Adventure in Alaska by George S. Elrick Whitman Big Little Book 2004 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 43)
- Lassie and the Shabby Sheik by George S. Elrick Whitman Big Little Book 2027 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 43)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E.: The Calcutta Affair by George S. Elrick Whitman Big Little Book 2011 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 43)
- Sir Lancelot by Dorothy Haas Whitman Big Little Book 1649 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 43)
- Walt Disney's Andy Burnett on Trial by Charles I. Coombs Whitman Big Little Book 1645 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 43)
- Wyatt Earp by Davis Lott Whitman Big Little Book 1644 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 43)